{
    "quizzes": [
      {
        "title": "week11",
        "questions": [
          {
            "index": 1,
            "question": "An action taken by an uninformed party to induce an informed party to reveal information is known as",
            "options": ["signalling", "screening", "informing", "heuristics"],
            "correct": "screening"
          },
          {
            "index": 2,
            "question": "The part of actual resources that can be developed profitably in the future are",
            "options": ["potential resources", "actual resources", "reserve resources", "stock resources"],
            "correct": "reserve resources"
          },
          {
            "index": 3,
            "question": "The limit on the consumption bundles that a consumer can afford is known as",
            "options": ["consumption constraint", "budget constraint", "bundle constraint", "affordability constraint"],
            "correct": "budget constraint"
          },
          {
            "index": 4,
            "question": "Mental short cut using emotion (gut feeling) to influence the decision is",
            "options": ["affect heuristic", "availability heuristic", "effort heuristic", "familiarity heuristic"],
            "correct": "affect heuristic"
          },
          {
            "index": 5,
            "question": "Those resources that are currently being used after surveying, quantification and qualification are",
            "options": ["potential resources", "actual resources", "reserve resources", "stock resources"],
            "correct": "actual resources"
          },
          {
            "index": 6,
            "question": "The change in consumption that results when a price change moves the consumer along a given indifference curve to a point with a new marginal rate of substitution is known as",
            "options": ["income effect", "substitution effect", "indifference effect", "budget effect"],
            "correct": "substitution effect"
          },
          {
            "index": 7,
            "question": "An inferior good whose demand increases with price is called as",
            "options": ["Normal good", "Veblen good", "Giffen good", "Demand good"],
            "correct": "Giffen good"
          },
          {
            "index": 8,
            "question": "Which of these is not a property of indifference curves?",
            "options": [
              "Higher indifference curves are preferred to lower ones",
              "Indifference curves are downward-sloping",
              "Indifference curves cross at right angles",
              "Indifference curves are bowed inwards"
            ],
            "correct": "Indifference curves cross at right angles"
          },
          {
            "index": 9,
            "question": "An action taken by an informed party to reveal private information to an uninformed party is known as",
            "options": ["signalling", "screening", "informing", "heuristics"],
            "correct": "signalling"
          },
          {
            "index": 10,
            "question": "Simple strategies or mental processes used to quickly form judgments, make decisions, and find solutions to complex problems is known as",
            "options": ["signalling", "screening", "informing", "heuristics"],
            "correct": "heuristics"
          }
        ]
      }
    ]
  }
  